Finding Aid for the Carol Burnett Papers PASC.0066
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Television Projects, 1956-2005; Series 3.; 34 manuscript boxes; 56 flat boxes
  - Carol Burnett Show (The), 1966-1978; Subseries 4.; 9 manuscript boxes; 35 flat boxes
    - America The Beautiful (#0405) (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Guests: Pat Carroll, Art Carney. Parts: 1st Alto Sax, 2nd Alto Sax, 3rd Tenor Sax, 4th Tenor Sax, Baritone Sax, 1st Trumpet, 2nd Trumpet, 3rd Trumpet, 4th Trumpet, 1st Trombone, 2nd Trombone, 3rd Trombone, 4th Trombone, Violin (3 copies), Viola, Cello, Bass, Guitar, Percussion, Drums, Harp, Piano.
    - America The Beautiful (#0405) (Box 13, Folder 3)
      Guests: Pat Carroll, Art Carney. Master Score. Production Score.
    - Anyone Want To Dance? (#007) (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Guests: Carol & Imogene Coca. Parts: 1st Alto Sax, 2nd Alto Sax, 3rd Tenor Sax, 4th Tenor Sax, 1st Trumpet, 2nd Trumpet, 3rd Trumpet, 4th Trumpet, 1st Trombone, 2nd Trombone, 3rd Trombone, 4th Trombone, Violin (orig. + 3 copies), Viola, Cello, Bass, Guitar, Percussion (orig. + 2 copies), Drums, Harp, Piano.
    - Anyone Want To Dance? (#007), undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
      Guests: Carol & Imogene Coca. Master Score; Production Score (orig. + 2 copies).
    - Applause, Nightclub Act #1 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      Artists: Carol & Jim. Parts: Alto Sax 1, Alto Sax 2, Tenor Sax 3, Tenor Sax 4, Baritone Sax 5, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 3, Trumpet 4, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Violin (3 copies), Violin 4, Viola, Cello, Bass, Guitar, Percussion, Drums.
    - Applause, Nightclub Act #1 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      Artists: Carol & Jim. Master Score; Piano/Conductor Score (3 copies).
    - Aquarius, Nightclub Act #1 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      Parts: Alto Sax 1 TACET, Alto Sax 2 TACET, Tenor Sax 3 TACET, Tenor Sax 4 TACET, Baritone Sax TACET, Trumpet 1 TACET, Trumpet 2 TACET, Trumpet 3 TACET, Trumpet 4 TACET, Trombone 1 TACET, Trombone 2 TACET, Trombone 3 TACET, Violin (4 copies) Tacet 15 bars, Viola TACET, Cello TACET, Bass TACET, Percussion TACET, Drums TACET.
    - Aquarius, Nightclub Act #1 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      Master Score; Piano/Conductor Score (3 copies); Flute Solo with Guitar.
    - Be Happy (#0405) (Box 12, Folder 2)
      Parts: 1st Alto Sax, 2nd Alto Sax, 3rd Tenor Sax, 4th Tenor Sax, Baritone Sax, 1st Trumpet, 2nd Trumpet, 3rd Trumpet, 4th Trumpet, 1st Trombone, 2nd Trombone, 3rd Trombone, 4th Trombone, Violin (3 copies), Viola, Cello, Bass, Guitar, Percussion (2 copies), Drums, Harp, Piano.
    - Be Happy (#0405) (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Guests: Pat Carroll, Art Carney. Artists: Pat Carroll, Carol Burnett. Master Score, Conductor Score (2 copies).
    - Big Slush (#0106) (Box 37, Folder 5)
      Parts: Reed 1, Reed 2, Reed 3, Reed 4, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Harp, Bass, Drums, Guitar, Percussion (orig. + 3 copies).
    - Big Slush (#0106) (Box 38, Folder 11)
      "The Slush": Stan Freeman, ASCAP Punkin Publishing. Conductor Score (orig.); Master Score; Conductor Score (orig. + 3 copies); Return of Vocal (from Slush Prod.) (orig. + 8 copies).
    - Boffo (#0106) (Box 37, Folder 2)
      Parts: Reed 1, Reed 2, Reed 3, Reed 4, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Harp, Bass, Drums, Guitar, Percussion (orig. + 2 copies).
    - Boffo (#0106) (Box 38, Folder 8)
      Master Score; Conductor Score (orig. + 2 copies).
    - Broadway Show Medley (#003), undated (Box 5, Folder unknown container)
      Guests: Jim Nabors. Artist: Carol & Jim Nabors. Master Score; Conductor Score (club version #23); Lead Sheet (revised).
    - Broadway Show Medley T.V. (#003) (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Guests: Jim Nabors. Parts: 1st Alto Sax, 2nd Alto Sax, 3rd Tenor Sax, 4th Tenor Sax, 5th Baritone Sax, 1st Trumpet, 2nd Trumpet, 3rd Trumpet, 4th Trumpet, 1st Trombone, 2nd Trombone, 3rd Trombone, 4th Trombone, Violin (orig. + 4 copies), Viola, Cello, Guitar, Harp, Bass, Percussion (orig. + 2 copies), Drums, Piano.
    - Broadway Show Medley T.V. (#003), undated (Box 5, Folder unknown container)
      Guests: Jim Nabors. Master Score; Conductor Score (orig. + 2 copies).
    - Broadway Show Medley, Part 2 (#003), undated (Box 5, Folder unknown container)
      Guests: Jim Nabors. Artist: Carol & Jim Nabors. Master Score.
    - Call The Doctor (#0106) (Box 37, Folder 11)
      Parts: Reed 1, Reed 2, Reed 3, Reed 4, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Harp, Bass, Drums, Percussion (orig. + 3 copies), Guitar.
    - Call The Doctor (#0106) (Box 38, Folder 17)
      "Call The Doctor": Stan Freeman, ASCAP Punkin Publishing. Conductor Score (orig.); Master Score; Conductor Score (orig. + 3 copies).
    - Can't Get a Man With a Gun (#19), undated (Box 52, Folder 5)
      [Carol Burnett Show] Conductor score (2 copies); Production. Orchestral parts: 1-5 Reed; 1-4 Trumpet; 1-3 Trombone; 1-2 Percussion; Guitar; Harp; A-B Violin (3 copies); Viola; Cello; Bass; 1-2 Drums; Piano.
    - Can't Get A Man With A Gun, undated (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Charwoman, undated (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Doin' Chores (#309) (Box 15, Folder 3)
      Guests: Andy Griffith. Master Score. (Conductor Score missing.)
    - Doing What Comes Naturally, undated (Box 52, Folder 4)
      [Carol Burnett Show] Manuscript: vocals.
    - Don't Fence Me In (Box 27, Folder 6)
      Parts: Viola (orig. + copy), Cello (orig. + copy), Bass (orig.), Reed 5 (orig.), Reed 4 (orig.), Guitar, Violin A & B (orig.), Reed 1, 2, 3 (orig.), Trumpet 1, 2, 3, 4 (orig.), Trombone 1, 2, 3 (orig.), Percussion 1, 2 (orig.), Guitar (orig.), Flute/Oboe/Bassoon/Horn, Harp (orig. + copy) TACET, Trombone 3, Violin A & B (2 copies).
    - Don't Grab (#0106) (Box 36, Folder 4)
      Parts: Reed 1, Reed 2, Reed 3, Reed 4, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Harp, Bass, Drums, Percussion, Guitar.
    - Don't Grab (#0106) (Box 38, Folder 4)
      Master Score; Conductor Score (orig. + 3 copies).
    - Don't Grab A Button (#0106) (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Don't Grab A Button (30106) (Box 36, Folder 6)
      Parts: Reed 1 (orig. + 1 copy), Reed 2 (orig. + 1 copy), Reed 3 (orig. + 1 copy), Reed 4 (orig. + 1 copy), Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Harp, Bass, Drums, Percussion, Guitar.
    - Dying Grab (#0106) (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Dying Grab (#0106) (Box 38, Folder 12)
      "Sue Grabbed A Rose": Stan Freeman, ASCAP Punkin Publishing. Master Score; Conductor Score (orig. + 3 copies); Lead Sheet (5 copies).
    - Entre Act Pt. 1 (#11), undated (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - For All We Know, If I Could Write A Song (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Parts: Voices (2 copies), 1st Trumpet, 2nd Trombone, 1st Trombone, 2nd Trumpet, Guitar (2 copies), Alto Flute, Drums, Violin (4 copies), Cello, Viola, Piano, Harp, 2nd Percussion, 1st Percussion.
    - For All We Know, If I Could Write A Song (Box 32, Folder 6)
      Master Score; Conductor (2 copies).
    - For Me - Intro (#003) (Box 4, Folder unknown container)
      Guests: Jim Nabors. Parts: Alto Flute (orig.), 1st Alto Sax, 2nd Alto Sax, 3rd Tenor Sax, 4th Tenor Sax, Baritone Sax, 1st Trumpet, 2nd Trumpet, 3rd Trumpet, 4th Trumpet, 1st Trombone, 2nd Trombone, 3rd Trombone, 4th Trombone, Violin (orig. + 4 copies), Cello, Viola, Bass, Drums, Percussion, Piano, Harp.
    - For Me - Intro (#003), undated (Box 5, Folder unknown container)
      Guests: Jim Nabors. Master Score; Conductor Score.
    - For Me (#003) (Box 4, Folder unknown container)
      Guests: Jim Nabors. Artist: Carol - Choir. Parts: 1st Alto Sax, 2nd Alto Sax, 3rd Tenor Sax, 4th Tenor Sax, 5th Baritone Sax, 1st Trumpet, 2nd Trumpet, 3rd Trumpet, 4th Trumpet, 1st Trombone, 2nd Trombone, 3rd Trombone, 4th Trombone, Cello, Viola, Violin (orig. + 4 copies), Bass, Guitar, Drums, Piano, Percussion (orig. + 2 copies), Harp.
    - For Me (#003), undated (Box 5, Folder unknown container)
      Guests: Jim Nabors. Artist: Carol - Choir. Master Score; Conductor Score (orig. + 2 copies).
    - Girls (#0106) (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Girls (#0106) (Box 38, Folder 1)
      Guest: Ken Berry. Artists: Ken Berry & Dancers. Stan Freeman, ASCAP, Punkin Music. Master Score; Conductor Score (orig. + 8 copies).
    - Golden Earaches (#028) (Box 9, Folder 1)
      Guests: Sid Caesar, Barbara McNair Parts: Alto Sax 1, Alto Sax 2, Tenor Sax 3, Tenor Sax 4, Baritone Sax, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trumpet 4, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Violin (orig. + 3 copies), Viola, Cello, Bass, Guitar, Percussion (orig. + 1 copy), Drums, Harp, Piano, Additional violin part for song: "Csardas".
    - Golden Earaches (#028), undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Guests: Sid Caesar, Barbara McNair. Master Score. Conductor Score (Orig. +).
    - Good Old Sounds (#0311) (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Artist: Nanette Fabray. Guests: Trini Lopez, Nanette Fabray. Parts: Sax 1, Sax 2, Sax 3, Sax 4, Sax 5, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trumpet 4, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Violin (3 copies), Viola, Cello, Bass, Guitar, Percussion (3 copies), Drums, Harp, Piano.
    - Good Old Sounds (#0311) (Box 17, Folder 1)
      Artist: Nanette Fabray. Guests: Trini Lopez, Nanette Fabray. Master Score; Conductor Score.
    - Grab Under (#0106) (Box 37, Folder 10)
      Parts: Reed 1 TACET, Reed 2, Reed 3 TACET, Reed 4, Trumpet 1 TACET, Trumpet 2 TACET, Trumpet 3 TACET, Trombone 1 TACET, Trombone 2 TACET, Trombone 3 TACET, Trombone 4 TACET, Harp, Bass TACET, Drums TACET, Percussion TACET, Guitar TACET.
    - Grab Under (#0106) (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Guess Who/Turn Around, If I Could Write A Song (Box 31, Folder 3)
      Parts: Vocal Conductor Score (2 copies), Voices (2 copies), Bass, Cello, Viola, 1st Rhythm Guitar, 1st Trumpet, 1st Trombone, 2nd Trombone, 2nd Trumpet, Flute, 2nd Electric Guitar, Drums, Percussion (2 copies), Violin (4 copies), Piano.
    - Guess Who/Turn Around, If I Could Write A Song (Box 32, Folder 8)
      Master Score.
    - Guest Taping Schedule, 1969-1970; 5 pages (Box 22, Folder 22)
      Contains Guest Taping Schedule that includes Tape and Air Date, Production # and Guests; shows listed from April 25, 1969-May 1, 1970; 34 shows total. Also contains two 4"x 5 1/2" handwritten notes on The Carol Burnett Show, Charlene Del Sardo stationary with a list of movie titles ("Butch Cassidy," "Easy Rider," "Midnight Cowboy," "Charley") and the phone number of Gary Morton.
    - Gypsy Finale (#028) (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Guests: Sid Caesar, Barbara McNair. Parts: Alto Sax 1, Alto Sax 2, Tenor Sax 3, Tenor Sax 4, Baritone Sax, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trumpet 4, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Violin (3 copies), Viola, Cello, Bass, Guitar, Percussion, Piano, Drums, Harp.
    - Gypsy Finale (#028), undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Guests: Sid Caesar, Barbara McNair. Master Score. Production Score.
    - Habañera, undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
      Conductor score. Orchestral parts: 1-5 Reed; 1-4 Trumpet; 1-3 Trombone; Guitar; Harp; A-C Violin; Viola; Cello; Bass; Piano; Drums.
    - Habañera (#2275), udated (Box 57, Folder 10)
      Conductor score; original folder marked "Key D [flat] 2275."
    - Hands, Nightclub Act #1 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      Artists: Carol & Jim. Parts: Alto Sax 1, Alto Sax 2, Tenor Sax 3, Tenor Sax 4, Baritone Sax 5, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trumpet 4, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Violin (orig. + 2 copies), Viola, Cello, Bass, Guitar, Percussion (orig. + 3 copies), Drums.
    - Hands, Nightclub Act #1 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Happiness is a Thing Called Joe, undated (Box 51, Folder 9)
      Orchestral parts: 1-4 Reed; 1-2 Trumpet; Trombone; Guitar; Bass; Vibes; Drums.
    - Happiness Is A Thing Called Joe, undated (Box 59, Folder 7)
      Conductor score-Piano (4 copies).
    - High-Tone Hoe Down (#309) (Box 14, Folder 2)
      Guests: Andy Griffith. Parts: Sax 1, Sax 2, Sax 3, Sax 4, Sax 5, 1st Trumpet, 2nd Trumpet, 3rd Trumpet, 4th Trumpet (Trumpet nterlude), 1st Trombone, 2nd Trombone, 3rd Trombone, 4th Trombone (Trombone Interlude), Violin (3 copies), Viola, Cello, Bass, Guitar, Lead Sheet, Percussion (2 copies), Drums, Harp, Piano.
    - High-Tone Hoe Down (#309) (Box 15, Folder 2)
      Guests: Andy Griffith. Master Score; Conductor Score.
    - Hospital Grab (#0106) (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Hospital Grab (#0106) (Box 38, Folder 9)
      Master Score; Conductor Score (orig. + 3 copies); Lead Sheet.
    - How Lovely (#3), undated (Box 53, Folder 5)
      Orchestral parts: 1-5 Reed; 1-4 Trumpet; 1-3 Trombone; 1-2 Percussion; Guitar; Harp; A-C Violin; Viola; Cello; Bass.
    - How Lovely (#3), undated (Box 53, Folder 6)
      Conductor score (3 copies). Orchestral parts: 1-5 Reed; 1-4 Trumpet; 1-3 Trombone; 1-2 Percussion; Guitar; Harp; A-C Violin; Viola; Cello; Bass; Basson; Flute. Original folder marked: "2275 Key D flat."
    - How Lovely II The Open, undated (Box 57, Folder 11)
      Conductor score (2 copies). Original folder marked: "Carol Burnett How Lovely 3."
    - I Can't Say No, udated (Box 57, Folder 8)
      Conductor score. Originally in binder with other songs Sweet Georgia Brown and Mongolier-Intro marked "605."
    - I Feel Pretty, Nightclub Act #1 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      Parts: Alto Sax 1, Alto Sax 2, Tenor Sax 3, Tenor Sax 4, Baritone Sax 5, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trumpet 4, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Violin A, Violin B, Violin C, Cello, Bass, Guitar, Percussion (3 copies), Drums.
    - I Feel Pretty, Nightclub Act #1 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      Master Score; Lead Sheet; Piano/Conductor Score (3 copies).
    - I Grabbed (#0106) (Box 37, Folder 1)
      Parts: Reed 1, Reed 2, Reed 3, Reed 4, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Harp, Bass, Drums, Percussion (orig. + 2 copies), Guitar.
    - I Grabbed (#0106) (Box 38, Folder 7)
      Master Score; Conductor Score (orig. + 3 copies); Lead Sheet (orig.).
    - If I Could Write A Song (Box 29, Folder 2)
      Parts: Voices (2 copies), Bass, Cello, Viola, Rhythm Guitar 1, Violin (4 copies), Trumpet 2, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trumpet 1, Flute, Electric Guitar 2, Drums, Percussion (2 copies), Piano.
    - If I Could Write a Song (Box 32, Folder 2)
      Master Score; Vocal Conductor.
    - If I Could Write A Song[?] (Box 31, Folder 4)
      Parts: Voices (orig. + 2 copies), Piano, Bass, 1st Trumpet, 1st Trombone, 1st Rhythm Guitar, 2nd Electric Guitar, Violin (4 copies), Viola, Cello, Percussion (2 copies), Drums, Alto Sax, 2nd Trombone, 2nd Trumpet.
    - I'll Never Fall In Love Again, Nightclub Act #1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      Artists: Carol & Jim. Parts: Alto Sax 1, Alto Sax 2, Tenor Sax 3, Tenor Sax 4, Baritone Sax 5, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trumpet 4, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Violin (3 copies), Violin 4, Viola, Cello, Bass, Percussion (2 copies), Drums.
    - I'll Never Fall In Love Again, Nightclub Act #1 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - I'm an Indian Too, undated (Box 52, Folder 3)
      Conductor score: Production.
    - Intro 17 (#0106) (Box 37, Folder 4)
      Parts: Reed 1 (orig. + 1 copy), Reed 2 (orig. + 1 copy), Reed 3 (orig. + 1 copy), Reed 4 (orig. + 1 copy), Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Harp, Bass, Drums, Percussion, Guitar TACET.
    - Intro 17 (#0106) (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - It's Too Late, If I Could Write A Song (Box 30, Folder 2)
      Parts: Vocal Conductor, Percussion, Drums, 2nd Trombone, 1st Trombone, 2nd Trumpet, 1st Trumpet, Flute, 1st Rhythm Guitar, 2nd Electric Guitar, Bass, Piano, Violin (4 copies), Viola, Cello, Vocal Conductor, Voices (2 copies).
    - It's Too Late, If I Could Write A Song (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Jazz Band Ball (#0405), undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Guests: Pat Carroll, Art Carney. Parts: 1st Alto Sax, 2nd Alto Sax, 3rd Tenor Sax, 4th Tenor Sax, Baritone Sax, 1st Trumpet, 2nd Trumpet, 3rd Trumpet, 4th Trumpet, 1st Trombone, 2nd Trombone, 3rd Trombone, 4th Trombone, Violin (3 copies), Viola, Cello, Bass, Guitar, Percussion (2 copies), Drums, Harp, Piano.
    - Jazz Band Ball (#0405) (Box 13, Folder 1)
      Guests: Pat Carroll, Art Carney. Master Score. Conductor Score (2 copies).
    - Let's Hear It, undated (Box 51, Folder 7)
      Orchestral part: Bass.
    - Lily's Entrance (#0106) (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Lily's Entrance (#0106) (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Lucretia Intro (#0422) (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Guests: Chita Rivera, Bob Newhart. Parts: Alto Sax 1, Alto Sax 2, Tenor Sax 3, Tenor Sax 4, Baritone Sax 5, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trumpet 4, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Violin (3 copies), Viola, Cello, Bass, Guitar, Percussion (3 copies), Drums, Harp, Electric Piano.
    - Lucretia Intro (#0422) (Box 20, Folder 1)
      Guests: Chita Rivera, Bob Newhart. Master Score; Production Score (3 copies).
    - Maybe (#0422) (Box 19, Folder 2)
      Artists: Harvey Korman, Carol Burnett. Parts: Alto Sax 1, Alto Sax 2, Tenor Sax 3, Tenor Sax 4, Baritone Sax, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trumpet 4, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Violin (3 copies), Viola, Cello, Bass, Guitar, Percussion (3 copies), Drum, Harp, Piano, Lead Sheet.
    - Maybe (#0422) (Box 21, Folder 1)
      Artists: Harvey Korman, Carol Burnett. Master Score; Conductor Score.
    - Meantime, udated (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Meantime, 1962; piano, bass, drums, percussion, guitar, alto sax, tenor sax, baritone sax, trumpet, trombone, violin, viola, cello, clarinet, bass clarinet. (Box 652)
    - Meantime, undated (Box 652)
      [Carol Burnett Show] Orchestral parts: 1-5 Reed; 1-4 Trumpet; 1-3 Trombone; 1-2 Percussion; Guitar; Harp; A-C Violin; Viola; Cello; Bass; Piano.
    - Meantime (Box 652)
      Ponductor score--Piano.
    - Meantime (Box 652)
      Ozalid score
    - Meantime (#9), undated (Box 52, Folder 2)
      Orchestral parts: 1-5 Reed; 1-4 Trumpet; 1-3 Trombone; 1-2 Percussion; Guitar; Harp; A-C Violin; Viola; Cello; Bass. Conductor score: Piano (3 copies).
    - Medley - Face and 2nd Time (#028) (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Parts: Alto Sax 1, Alto Sax 2, Tenor Sax 3, Tenor Sax 4, Baritone Sax, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trumpet 4, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Violin (orig. + 3 copies), Viola, Cello, Bass, Guitar, Percussion (orig. + 1 copy), Drums, Harp, Piano.
    - Medley-Face and 2nd Time (#028), undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
      Master Score. Production Score (Orig. + 2 copies).
    - Miss Las Vegas, Nightclub Act #1 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      Parts: Alto Sax 1, Alto Sax 2, Tenor Sax 3, Tenor Sax 4, Baritone Sax 5, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trumpet 4, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Violins (4 copies), Viola, Cello, Bass, Guitar, Drums, Percussion (2 copies).
    - Miss Las Vegas, Nightclub Act #1 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Miss Non-Speller (Box 28, Folder 3)
      Nightclub Act #1. Master Score + New 7 Page + New 8 Page; Piano/Conductor Score (orig. + 2 copies).
    - Miss Non-Speller, Nightclub Act #1 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      Parts: Reed 1 (+ orig.), Reed 2 (+ orig.), Reed 3 (Addition Rewrite), Reed 4 (+ orig.), Reed 5 (+ orig.), Trumpet 1 (+ orig.), Trumpet 2 (+ orig.), Trumpet 3 (+ orig.), Trumpet 4 (1 copy + orig.), Trombone 1 (+ orig.), Trombone 2 (+ orig.), Trombone 3 (1 copy + orig.), Violin A (orig. + 2 copies), Violin B (+ orig.), Viola (+ orig.), Cello (+ orig.), Bass (+ orig.), Guitar (+ orig.), Percussion 1 & 2 (orig. + 2 copies), Harp (+ orig.), Horn TACET, Flute (3 copies) TACET, Bassoon (3 copies + orig.) TACET, Oboe (3 copies) TACET.
    - Miss Non-Speller, Nightclub Act #1 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      Parts: Alto Sax 1, Alto Sax 3, Tenor Sax 1 TACET, Tenor Sax 2, Baritone Sax 5, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trumpet 4, Trombone 1, Trombone 2 TACET, Trombone 3 TACET, Percussion 1 TACET, Bass, Guitar, Drums, Piano, Harp TACET, Guitar, Violin A (2 copies) TACET, Violin B (2 copies) TACET, Viola TACET, Cello TACET, Bass, Guitar TACET, Bass (Addition), Drums (Addition).
    - Miss Non-Speller, Nightclub Act #1 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      Piano/Conductor Score (orig.); also Bar 39 & 40 pencil original Master Score.
    - Mongolier-Intro, undated (Box 57, Folder 9)
      Conductor score. Originally in binder with other songs I Can't Say No and Sweet Georgia Brown marked "605."
    - My Magic Wand (#309) (Box 14, Folder 4)
      Guests: Andy Griffith. Parts: Piano Score, 1st Alto Sax, 2nd Alto Sax, 3rd Tenor Sax, 4th Tenor Sax, Baritone Sax, 1st Trumpet, 2nd Trumpet, 3rd Trumpet, 4th Trumpet, 1st Trombone, 2nd Trombone, 3rd Trombone, 4th Trombone, Violin (3 copies), Viola, Cello, Bass, Guitar, Percussion (3 copies), Drums, Harp.
    - My Magic Wand (#309) (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - My Romance (Box 27, Folder 8)
      Parts: Lead Sheet/Piano Score, Bass, Drums.
    - Nobody, undated (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Nobody (#19), undated (Box 51, Folder 10)
      Orchestral parts: 1-4 Reed; 1-3 Trumpet; 1-3 Trombone; 1-2 Percussion; Guitar; Harp; A-C Violin; Viola; Cello; Bass; Flute; Oboe; Bassoon; Horn.
    - Old Mac, undated (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Old Mac (#14), undated (Box 53, Folder 1)
      [Carol Burnett Show] Orchestral parts: 1-5 Reed; 1-4 Trumpet; 1-3 Trombone; 1-2 Percussion; Guitar; Harp; A-C Violin; Viola; Cello; Bass; Piano. Conductor score: Piano (2 copies).
    - Once In Love With Amy (#0105) (Box 34, Folder 1)
      Parts: Reed 1, Reed 2, Reed 3, Reed 4, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Violas, Celli, Harp, Bass, Drums, Guitar. Frank Music Co. (orig. + 100 pages).
    - Once In Love With Amy (#0105) (Box 35, Folder 3)
      Words & Music by Frank Loesser. Master Score; Conductor Score (orig. + 3 copies); Violins (orig. + 3 copies); Percussion (orig. + 3 copies).
    - Overture (#0106) (Box 36, Folder 5)
      Parts: Reed 1, Reed 2, Reed 3, Reed 4, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Harp, Bass, Drums, Guitar, Percussion (orig + 2 copies).
    - Overture (#0106) (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Overture (Carol's & Jim's Themes), Nightclub Act #1 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      Parts: Alto Sax 1, Alto Sax 2, Tenor Sax 3, Tenor Sax 4, Baritone Sax 5, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trumpet 4, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Violin (4 copies), Viola, Cello, Bass, Guitar, Percussion (3 copies), Drums, Harp, Piano.
    - Overture (Carol's & Jim's Themes), Nightclub Act #1 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      Conductor Score; Master Score.
    - Pata Cuan Cuan (#0311) (Box 16, Folder 2)
      Artists: Carol Burnett, Nanette Fabray, Trini Lopez. Parts: Alto Sax 1, Alto Sax 2, Tenor Sax 3, Tenor Sax 4, Baritone Sax, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trumpet 4, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Violin (3 copies), Cello, Viola, Lead Sheet, Rhythm (5 copies), Drums/Perc. (4 copies).
    - Pata Cuan Cuan (#0311) (Box 17, Folder 2)
      Artists: Carol Burnett, Nanette Fabray, Trini Lopez. Master Score; Production Score.
    - Patriotic Medley, Parts 1 and 2 (#0405) (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Guests: Pat Carroll, Art Carney. Artists: Carol Burnett, Patt Carroll, Harvey Korman, Art Carney. Parts: 1st Alto Sax, 2nd Alto Sax, 3rd Tenor Sax, 4th Tenor Sax, Baritone Sax, 1st Trumpet, 2nd Trumpet, 3rd Trumpet, 4th Trumpet, 1st Trombone, 2nd Trombone, 3rd Trombone, 4th Trombone, Violin (3 copies), Viola, Cello, Guitar, Bass, Percussion (2 copies), Drums, Harp, Piano (Parts 1 and 2).
    - Patriotic Medley, Parts 1 and 2 (#0405) (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Guests: Pat Carroll, Art Carney. Artists: Carol Burnett, Patt Carroll, Harvey Korman, Art Carney. Master Score. Conductor Score (2 copies).
    - Photograph, undated; 1 photograph; 11"x14", color (Box 16, Folder 4)